https://www.strettonscientific.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Skip to contentHomeTissue HomogenisationPrecellys EvolutionCryolys EvolutionPrecellys 24CryolysMinilysHomogenisation TubesLive Cell ImagingZenCELL Owl Live Cell ProcessingMicro Array ProcessingHybex MicroarrayThe Little DipperThe NoZone WorkspaceMai Tai Hybridization SystemContact
MenuHomeTissue HomogenisationPrecellys EvolutionCryolys EvolutionPrecellys 24CryolysMinilysHomogenisation TubesLive Cell ImagingZenCELL Owl Live Cell ProcessingMicro Array ProcessingHybex MicroarrayThe Little DipperThe NoZone WorkspaceMai Tai Hybridization SystemContactHome » Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyThis privacy policy explains how we use any information we collect about you, how you can tell us if you prefer to limit the use of that information and procedures that we have in place to safeguard your privacy.For the purposes of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the “Act”) the data controller is Stretton Scientific Limited of Stretton House, Highstairs Lane, Stretton, Derbyshire DE55 6FD.Summary of our Privacy PolicyYour privacy is extremely important to us so we only use the information you provide about yourself and your company when using this website to answer your enquiry or to help us to improve our service to you. We do not share this information with any third party except to the extent necessary to answer your enquiry if that enquiry requires the involvement of a third party. We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.The information we collectWe may collect and process the following data about you:Information that you provide by filling in forms on our site at www.strettonscientific.co.uk (our “Website”). This includes information provided when requesting a quotation for our services and registering to receive our email newsletter. This typically includes your name, your organisation’s name, your position, email address, business address and contact telephone number. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our site.If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.Stretton Scientific may ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them.Details of your visits to our site including, but not limited to, web server statistics, traffic data, location data and details of the web pages and resources that you access.Our use of IP addresses and cookiesWe may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to analyse aggregate information. This is statistical data about our users’ browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.For the same reason, we may obtain information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive. They help us to improve our site and to deliver a better and more personalised service. They enable us:To estimate our audience size and usage pattern.To store information about your preferences, and so allow us to customise our site according to user needs.To speed up your searches.To recognise you when you return to our site.You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to our site.How we protect your informationAll information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of data that you transmit to our site; any transmission is therefore at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict internal procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.We also keep your information confidential. The internal procedures of Stretton Scientific cover the storage, access and disclosure of your information.How we use your informationWe use information held about you in the following ways:To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes.To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.To allow you to access secure areas of our Website when you choose to do so.We may also use your data to provide you with information about goods and services which may be of interest to you and we may contact you about these by email, SMS, post or telephone.If you are an existing customer, we will only contact you by electronic means (e-mail or SMS) with information about goods and services similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale to you. If you are a new customer we will contact you by electronic means only if you have consented to this.If you do not want us to use your data in this way, please notify us by sending an email to info@strettonscientific.co.uk.When we might disclose your data to third partiesWe may disclose your personal information to third parties in a very limited number of circumstances:Where we engage the business services of a third party to provide services directly to Stretton Scientific. For example, we may use a mailing house to email promotional materials such as our email newsletter. Rest assured that any third parties are strictly prohibited from using your personal data for any other purposes.In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.If Stretton Scientific or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use at and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Stretton Scientific, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.Your RightsYou have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at info@strettonscientific.co.uk.Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our clients and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.Your consentBy submitting your information you consent to the use of that information as set out in this policy. If we change our privacy policy we will post the changes on this page, and may place notices on other pages of the Website, so that you may be aware of the information we collect and how we use it at all times. We will also e-mail you should we make any changes so that you may consent to our use of your information in that way. Continued use of the service will signify that you agree to any such changes.Owing to the global nature of the Internet infrastructure, the information you provide may be transferred in transit to countries outside the European Economic Area that do not have similar protections in place regarding your data and its use as set out in this policy. However, we have taken the steps outlined above to try to improve the security of your information. By submitting your information you consent to these transfers.Contact DetailsWe welcome your views about our website and our privacy policy. If you would like to contact us with any queries or comments please send an e-mail to info@strettonscientific.co.uk.If any of the information that you have provided to Stretton Scientific changes, for example if you change your e-mail address or if you wish to cancel your registration for receiving our monthly newsletter, please let us know by sending an e-mail to your Stretton Scientific contact or to info@strettonscientific.co.uk.
Enquiries
© Stretton Scientific Limited. All rights reserved.Terms of use       Privacy policy      Sitemap
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.Ok
